this is true university of texas a
couple of years ago one of the chemistry
majors uh did a study on all the
chemicals and some of the fast food
right it made national news because she
found an ingredient in mcribs also used
to make exercise mats
that's true that's so gross and if
you're in here tonight and you eat
mcribs you're probably like what
is an exercise man
like the more someone tries to convince
you of something the less i believe them
every time wendy's has a commercial like
we use 100 real chicken i'm like i
thought you did
now i'm not so sure
why do you have to advertise
100 chicken never frozen it is
definitely frozen
i'm ordering at 1am i hope you froze it
it's just been sitting there all day
i think it's too easy to eat terrible
that's what i think it is you know
because it wasn't that long ago where
it's like you want to eat bad you got a
couple places you can go to now they
compete with each other to see who can
offer something worse for you wendy's
has a sandwich called son of baconator
their food is having kids when they're
closed do you understand how bad that is
for you
that's how i ordered too i'm like uh
give me a baconator and one of his
children i don't know you got a boy that
usually tastes better
last time i was in florida this is real
by the way this is google information
after the show i'm in florida i'm
walking past a newspaper stand i look
into the stand the headline on the
newspaper reads local man robs wendy's
with alligator
what did you just say to me
i read it i still said that out loud it
was incredible
oh and also yeah that's all you want to
say you don't want to add any more to
that like i don't know maybe tell us if
the alligator was an accomplice or a
weapon how about that
for real
did this guy rob a wendy's with an
alligator or did this guy rob a wendy's
with an alligator
there's a huge difference
like did he start did you start a gang
with an alligator throw a bandana on it
he's like for the alligator boys now
let's get to a wendy's and make this
official
no
so
this is how i bought the paper and i
read the article and this is real he
used the alligator as a weapon okay
and when i read that i was like did he
at least hold it like a gun
right
he didn't
he threw it
through a drive-through window
yep
didn't see that one coming did y'all
you know who else did it the lady
at the drive-thru
so many things have to happen before you
can even throw an alligator
you have to
find it in the wild
also by the way how horrible is florida
that there is just alligators available
to you
what was even his qualifying material
was he looking for a specific type are
you just the first one he saw he was
like this is the one and he took it that
was it
so this is real
this happened
in florida a place connected to the
united states
where we are all living currently
grown man with a driver's license
found an alligator that day he didn't
even build a relationship with it
takes his new alligator and he seat belt
it into the back seat of his car
i assume
i just have no idea how else you keep it
from getting into the front seat and
biting you right
i don't
know if you guys know anything about
alligators but they kind of just do
whatever they want
[Music]
so he seatbelts this dinosaur into the
back seat
and he gets into the front seat and he's
like ah
i gotta make some money
scared the today
oh i could get a job and he goes no no
time
spent most my day on that alligator
thing
projects
i could rob someone
and go take a rob a place
those places have more money than
someone's
rob a bank and he goes no no they'll be
expecting that
he's thinking about it and then he's
thought he comes to the conclusion
wendy's
they have money and chili that's the
place so he drives his new alligator to
wendy's okay
pulls up to the drive-through and the
lady at the drive-thru is like hello how
can i help you today and he goes give me
all the money
and she just goes looks right at him and
goes uh no
you didn't even come inside
you failed at this robbery
and the dude is so mad he goes give me
the money in the register or i'll kill
you and she's from florida so she's not
afraid of death or whatever
she looks down at him she's like no if
you had a gun you would have shown it to
me already i call your bluff gotta hear
crazy guy go go go
he's seething matt at this point furious
and he's like you know what i don't have
a gun but hold on
and then he palmed an alligator
through the drive-through window
yup
he skipped so many steps in that robbery
if he had a list of things
he was supposed to do
he would have thrown the alligator
looked down and just been like oh no
i was supposed to threaten her with the
alligator first
by the way can you imagine being her
telling this guy off and he's like you
know what i don't have a gun and you're
like wow nailed it really doing it today
and then he leads back and starts
unbuckling the world's ugliest toddler
hey someone come and see this is wild
that you look back and an alligator is
flying
imagine being the car behind him
just
sitting there with your girlfriend
like what takes so long to make burgers
here
she's on her phone you're like do you
even care you look back from her and
then an alligator soars
from window to window
honey get off your phone they're
throwing alligators and new wendy's
this guy is crazy
she's on her phone like that doesn't
make sense they don't even serve
alligators here
what why am i with you
[Laughter]
[Music]
so
this dude is sitting there
awkwardly with no more alligators left
to play in the robbery
probably thinking to himself oh you
think if i asked for my alligator back
such a bad idea to throw it he didn't
even put a fanny pack on it like
maybe get some money while you're in
there i don't know
so
he drives off
yeah and he gets arrested immediately
he didn't even wear a mask
yeah he was like i'm in florida people
throw alligators i'll probably get lost
in the shuffle
uh no he didn't
they remembered him they arrested him
pretty hard afterwards
the end of the article is true it goes
no one was injured the alligator was
safely released back into the wild at
the very end of the article it read no
drug involvement suspected
oh yeah florida
that was your sober plan
what does the non-sober plan look like
do you ride a horse and the alligator
throws you
what happens i'm pretty patriotic myself
here's how patriotic i am i am a
vegetarian but i love kentucky fried
chicken
i don't even need it anymore i just
support it
[Music]
because we were poor we got here we
couldn't eat out first thing we ate out
was kentucky fried chicken my dad went
all out he got the bucket of chicken he
got the biscuits
and he also bought the coleslaw
and if you've been eating coleslaw your
whole life maybe you don't know this but
it is disgusting
there's always somebody somewhere like
no it's pretty good yeah and people on a
farm get used to the smell of poop
you can get used to horrible things
i don't know who thought that like you
know what this salad needs to be wet
let's make a wet salad
should it be clear wet no it should be
snotty wet it should be the most
disgusting thing
and see if people will eat it
so my dad noticed we weren't eating the
coleslaw like hey
why is nobody eating deco
we're like dad it doesn't taste good
like i don't care you have to eat it
because the white people lead it
and they cannot find out we're now white
people
they're gonna know when you talk
my dad's not going to sneak past any of
you where are you from sir boston
machuchin that's how he says
massachusetts
you guys like having fun
get yourself an empty bucket from the
colonel sanders
there's more
put a real live chicken in it
go to the window at kfc
[Music]
come here yeah
this chicken ain't done
[Applause]
i do that stuff too man
this lady in gatlinburg i don't know
how else to just
she looked like someone who might
frequent a long john silver's slash
kentucky fried chicken
like a two-in-one fast food restaurant i
don't know if you guys ever go to those
but
there's good people watching in there
too
any of them i don't care what the combo
is
for some reason the average redneck
brain can't seem to process that there
are two businesses operating behind one
counter and sharing the menu above and
the first time they see it it just
catches them off guard they're like okay
could i get it
okay do i need to be at this register if
i want chicken
is this like a food court or something
it's the same company i can order off of
both of them oh i didn't know that
well i'm getting a family meal deal i
get two sides could i get a side from
this side and then aside from that side
like if i could hurry up and decide
could i go from side to side from my
sides
i can i want to try that okay
um
well extra biscuits i mean i knew that
before i came in here and
what does long john silvers have hush
puppies what can i do that two breads oh
yeah look it up
i know it sounds like i'm really
exaggerating for the sake of stand-up
comedy but it's not as much as you think
okay
i promise if you go to any two-in-one
fast food restaurant just grab a seat
close to the register just within
earshot within five minutes you'll hear
some truckers spit out a sins that has
never been formed in the history of
words
because he's buckling under the pressure
of the line that's now foreign behind
him he's like oh god i'm sorry you guys
i just i hadn't even thought about tacos
and then i come in here and boom right
there they are next to the pizza
but if you can make wherever you go half
of it long john silver's like that's
where you're going to have the best time
all right
at any long john silvers you will hear a
grown man ask for extra crumbs
which is a new low for our society
and really racist humans now
if i've completely lost you long john
silver's it's a fast food seafood
restaurant and what they do is is they
take chicken and fish and they dip it in
their batter
and then they put it in the deep fryer
and when they flip it from the deep
fryer little pieces of that batter break
off and then a pile of those little
pieces form and then people go hey could
i get a scoop of the thing that right
there i want some of that stuff like the
garbage on the bottom i want some like
put some of that into my treasure chest
they get off and i was like did that guy
just ask for more crumbs
like i thought i might have misheard
right she pushes a button on the
register boop crumbs ten cents i was
like you gotta be kidding me how often
does this happen okay seriously
like i thought i could be witnessing the
first time in the history of long john
silver's where some guy was like listen
this is gonna sound a little crazy
but i'm a little short on cash and i
have a long drive ahead of me could you
maybe just put some of that stuff into a
cup i could snack on it while i'm on the
road i don't know
no people it happened so much that it
has been programmed into the register
and if that's the case right if whatever
you call that stuff has its own button
which i'm pretty sure we can all agree
was not in the original business plan
that tells me that there was a day
somewhere
that it went down right
and as a professional people watcher i'm
just mad i wasn't there to see it
you know because i just pictured some
toothless managers storming out of the
back hey somebody's gonna start paying
for these crunchies all right i can't be
giving this stuff away all day
if everybody's going to ask for it we
got to figure something out
let's just be honest y'all love free
stuff that's what it is ain't it
yeah it is that's why we had to get rid
of our tartar sauce pump and switch to
packets put them behind the counter
limit two per customer cause y'all were
pumping it right into your boats are you
kidding me
nobody needs that much tartar sauce
and i'm sick of dealing with it he tries
to slam the door but it's that metal
kitchen door right
10 minutes later no one's speaking
because you can still hear him in the
back ticked off i ain't selling down
tommy i'm sick of this
they don't pay me enough to put up with
this i'm so mad my hand's shaking i'm
supposed to bowl tonight now what
i'm done well i don't care if i said it
before i mean it this time you watch
as soon as i can afford that lift kitten
and luke bryan take it you ain't never
gonna see me again i'm out
well of course i'm going florida georgia
line's open and i ain't gonna miss that
they're the only dudes that can settle
me down right now
you do that for me
all right you take the nelly part
you make me wanna roll my window
[Music]
okay listen
obviously i've thought way too much
about a day that probably never happened
okay i'll give you that
but i have questions and i want them
answered
and the only people that can answer them
are those in charge of the yum brands
if you're not familiar with who they are
pizza hut taco bell kentucky fried
chicken long john silvers a w root beer
now i don't know what they're on
but they're on something okay
all their ideas whether it's for the
restaurant the two in one fast food
concept itself i feel like they just get
together in a big room
hey hey carl you got anything
um
there have been several occasions
where i was like
i want fried chicken and pizza at the
same time but
probably was not in a
stable position to drive two separate
places
can we do something about that
yeah i think we could do something about
that we could probably sell both of
those here right yeah all right we can
put that down save some money on rent
phil what do you guys got
okay we're representing pizza hut and um
you know the doughy part around the
outside of the pizza the crust the crust
dude i told you it was called the crust
what if
and i'm just spitballing here we remove
the crust
and replace it with a ring of soft
pretzel pigs in a blanket and if we
can't do that could we just fill it with
cheese
well we can certainly look into one of
those if not all of them i think those
are all good ideas our audience would
certainly enjoy
ricky what about you
i've always wanted to make taco shells
out of doritos
that's what i'm talking about that needs
to be
put that down first we got to figure
that one out first maybe the greatest
idea that's ever come out of these
summits
let's start with nacho cheese cool ranch
in the fourth quarter people love little
red and green flecks on their taco
shells at christmas i love it i love
everything i'm hearing
we do have a set greeting though the
greeting is scripted you can't say hello
your own way you got to say it just like
this welcome to burger king really thank
your order
why don't you try you try it young man
okay sir um
what are you doing here
i'm not quite but you'll get it
you know if i go to burger king if i get
an order of onion rings there's always a
couple of french fries mixed in there
with them
always but if i get the french fries
there's never any onion rings mixed in
there
are they in the same pile or ante
i'm mystified by that
you ever lied all these places you're
hungry and you're in a hurry and you're
watching the guy working back there and
by the way he's moving you're pretty
sure he's underwater
i get drowsy watching them work
i get up there i'm falling asleep i'll
have a i have a hamburger what time is
it
sometimes i'll screw up the girl screw
them you know yeah i'm going to get a
i'm going to get a mc whopper
yeah mc whopper
with mashed potatoes and
a
the heineken heineken
supersize the biggie
you know what make it a schlitz
can i change my order
you ever try to change your order oh man
they look at you like you ask them to
rewire the pentagon
[Laughter]
we got a situation over here
we got a code red
yeah this man he's not going to eat the
things he said he would eat it
originally
what am i supposed to do now
push the buttons show me which ones
shift alt end to delete escape start
over well remember what do you want
get it right this time
this is hard what i'm doing is hard
burger king they don't mind the special
order right extra pickle that's their
slogan that's not their slogan
that's not
that's why i'm not in the slogan writing
business have it your way that's their
slogan have it your way that's still
there's look you know i like doing
burger king oh you know what i want i
want a whopper with cheese but i want
the top bun on the bottom and the bottom
bottom of the top
yeah that's my way i want the top bound
on the bottom the bottom of the top
don't just think you can flip it upside
down i know the difference
and i want you to cut into eight pieces
like a pizza
i'm gonna eat it with a spork
you got sporks i hope
a w's got sporks
i like burger king better than
mcdonald's not because the food's any
better because i'm really immature and
every time i go to burger king i get an
onion ring in my fries that's a good day
you don't even know you got it till you
get back to the table
you have your tray you're like oh do you
want to sit at this booth right here oh
that's fine oh i didn't pay for this
who's the king now huh
i'm gonna put it to the side save it for
later
little ketchup circle of protection
around it
just the opposite if you get a fry on
your onion rings you're a little mad
about it you know
it's a waste of space you're up at the
counter where's the manager my crown
falls off i don't want to talk about it
stuff fits
i found this out while i was in oklahoma
did you know if you go through a
drive-through fast food restaurant
without a car
they'll get mad
this is a true story y'all whenever i
work a club on land it's the club owner
responsibility for my accommodations and
this club owner has put me up in a hotel
that's right across the parking lot
you'll notice i didn't say street right
it's right across the parking lot from a
burger king and i stumbled over there
one night midnight one o'clock after a
show i was a little bit inebriated and
um okay i won't lie to you i was a lot
of inebriated
but i knew better than to drive and i
got to the to the burger king and the
doors were locked y'all but but that
drive-thru was open
[Music]
i was just standing at the speaker
and that woman that lives in that box
right there
said welcome to burger king might take
your order i was like yeah i want a
whopper with cheese
and i want a small fry
and i wanted a coke
and she said are you in a car
i was like i don't know can you see me
[Music]
she wouldn't serve me
yeah i had to hitchhike in the
drive-through
oh hey dude
could you take me to that first window
right there
i can help with gas
he wouldn't do it i had to get a taxi
56 for a whopper
the other day
i wasn't feeling great about old andrew
hopps you know feeling pretty bad about
myself
so i did something i regret
i went to burger king
yeah i know
i regret it too
and i order my food
thinking like
i deserve this is just what i asked for
because i asked for it
[Music]
and over the intercom this little voice
says hey
for a dollar
would you like
two cookies
sorry i get a little emotional with this
one
and i told him i've done nothing today
to deserve two cookies
i drive around to the window
and there he is
with two cookies
and he says to me
son
sometimes we all deserve
[Music]
two cookies
and i am here to tell you
that the king of all burgers is a just
and merciful king
and if we will but humble ourselves he
will provide here's something that
happened to me a while back that was
half stupid half just cracked me up
there's a town in alabama that when i'm
driving down to the gulf of mexico you
have to go through and it's spelled
really weird it's about e-a-u-f-a-u-l-a
has anybody ever heard of this probably
well
for over 40 years i've been going
through this town and i never learned
how to pronounce it it's driving me
crazy so i figured you know what doggone
it next time i want to stop and get a
local that's the best way isn't it
so get a local teach me so i stopped in
the first building i could find go in
sweet little lady behind the counter i
go ma'am you got to help me
can you please tell me where i am and
say it slowly so i'll understand
she's like all right
[Music]
thank you i figured that he was silent
i got a buddy he's got him everywhere
right tattoos all the way up to his neck
two full sleeves the works he's always
complaining to me though about not being
able to get a job he's like i don't get
it man i'm like dude what's not to get
you got a tattoo of a demon on your neck
you should have been smarter about this
and gotten the tattoo of your resume
it's like hey check it out shift lead to
burger king 0408
i dropped a couple french fries
anybody been pulled over recently and
deserved it anybody do that nobody
admits to it see
i deserved it it was my fault i admit
that it was my fault i was driving by
myself in the carpooling which is
terrible i was late to a gig and i took
a shot got pulled over got cut all right
and my first instinct is to maybe make
up a lie or just joke around with a
police officer see if i can get out of
it you know but i couldn't come up with
a lie for driving by myself in the
carpool lane
so i just panicked and i was like oh no
i left my baby at burger king again
and i don't know why i said again
like i do this all the time
don't worry officer i know the drill uh
he laughed he thought it was funny but
then he wrote me a ticket because that
doesn't work right and i don't know what
was gonna happen like what was my end
game on this like my mind immediately
goes like worst case scenario right like
i'm getting a police escort back to
burger king
no way i'm just praying there's an
abandoned baby there
that i can borrow for a few or whatever
then i'm texting my friends like drop
your kid off at burger king
quick
my uncle tax texts back immediately yeah
i'll do it
father of the year
but he only has a 17 year old daughter
that's
not what i meant
i mean
me and the cop get out of the car and
she just goes hey daddy
this is gonna be way worse than a minor
traffic infraction i think take me home
daddy okay shut your mouth rose
i love advertisement especially when
advertising is unintentionally funny
i'll give an example i'm driving by a
burger king right the birking sign reads
now hiring closers but a windstorm had
hit and the sea had fallen off the sun
i gotta wait for the bad spellers on
that joke
i remember the last day that i was
honest this woman she started opening up
right like not in a good way emotionally
in a very unkind way
she's like you know when i was eight
years old my dad went out to get
hamburgers for the whole family and
never came back and i was like oh my
those must have been some amazing
hamburgers
do you remember where he went
i want some did he help it we should
find your father
could you imagine a hamburger so good
where you just leave your family
you you take one bite i'm not going back
i won't go back
you gotta go back
what about your kids
chick-fil-a chick-fil-a required to say
with pleasure and my pleasure to any
anything everything it's in their
training i have two straws here you go
thank you my pleasure i think you're
overestimating this transaction
it can't be your pleasure
oh no i uh i drive that car i drive that
subaru around to a lot of a lot of
stand-up comedy gigs and so i'm driving
a lot and i'm constantly afraid that i'm
gonna fall asleep
at the wheel like i don't know if this
happens to you guys but i've tried
everything i get drowsy as soon as i
start driving so i've tried sunflower
seeds i've tried those little energy
drinks and nothing has worked
until now i figured out the best way to
stay awake and alert
before i drive anywhere
i stop
at jack-in-the-box
yeah
and i order myself two
dirty tacos
the kind that are so greasy you can see
through them
because nothing keeps you on the edge of
your seat
[Music]
like holding back diarrhea
you are awake and you are alert
[Music]
it's crazy
i do like exploring new places and your
community is no doubt what a beautiful
place listen i get to go to some of the
most beautiful place oh i was just i was
in mexico right and i've been there a
bunch and but i've never had like
mexican cuisine because they don't have
the chalupas and whatnot there so i had
to go
numero cuatro um and so i went to the
taxi driver and i said sir please take
me uh pour for uh uh to where the locals
eat
and this
fella
took me
to a five guys
do you have five guys where you live all
right
here's a little tip from me to you don't
order the large french fry at five guys
it comes in a wheelbarrow it's huge
that's the only french fry that's bad
for your back
so i'm in this little town eating eating
idaho pretty much i'm eating this stuff
and this lady
bless her
[Music]
i'm gonna describe this lady to you with
love in my heart she's leaving the five
guys with a bag of five guys in each
hand
and i'm thinking that's like 10 guys
that's a lot of guys
it's a little math joke um
i will describe her to you as my nana
would have described her
with love and respect in my heart
she was a big boned woman
we on the same page you know what i mean
when i say big bone woman now
full disclosure i did not see any bones
but surely they were present
some things we take on faith
she's leaving the five guys bag of five
guys at each hand as she leaves there
was an incident i'm trying to think how
to make this friend oh oh oh she had a
blowout
not sure what you're cheering for
[Music]
she blew out her croc you know what a
croc is everybody knows a croc like a
foam rubber garden and slipper that
four-year-old white kids wear to the
pool okay
the official shoe of connor you're with
me okay right
i don't know what kind of load the croc
is rated for
now load's an engineering word i'm not
being disrespectful
[Music]
i don't know what that number is
but it was exceeded that day
right there in the in the cinco ombres
right there
[Laughter]
thanks for digging my spanish um
now i don't know all the science words
but she made a move i would call it a
plant pivot
she was able to complete the maneuver
just fine the croc
not so much
it accepted the plant
resisted the pivot
and i guess the compression and the
torsion and the shearing force and the
friction co i don't know it turns into
dust
there's crock dust in there
that was preceded by a hissing noise
and she looked at me i'm like don't look
at me senor that's all you no i'm
wearing two shoes you got a croc foot
and a barefoot
but i try to be helpful i said so what
you want to do maybe is cut back to
let's say
uno one one uno bag of five guys
head over there to the peso last shoe
store
[Music]
and get some grown-up shoes
so do any of you guys go to in-n-out
burger you guys have heard of it
yes oh my gosh i love it i i'm from
minnesota where we don't have it and i
live in l.a now and i like i think it's
super cool and when my family was coming
to visit i wanted to impress them so i
was like oh my gosh you guys we have to
go to in-n-out burger it's so cool and i
was amping them up i was talking about
it for months and months and months and
i was like they have a secret menu you
have to know what's on the menu they
don't tell you have to know you know
and i was just super excited and they
were super excited so when the plane
landed we i took them directly to
in-n-out burger and we get there i'm so
excited they're so excited we get in
line get up to the line
and i cannot remember the name
of the secret menu item
right do you guys know what it is
animal style right i could not remember
so i'm in line and my family's watching
and i'm just staring at this cashier and
i'm just like
we would like
four burgers
unicorn style
i stared on the cashier and he goes
okay
i was like okay and he was like
it's like okay
all right we did it this is great we're
doing it yes he goes he goes to make the
burgers my family's excited 20 minutes
go by
we get our burgers it's the same cashier
made sure to deliver them to us and he
shoves this box of burgers towards us
and it's four burgers
and they eat chef
just one french fries
and i'm looking at the cashier and he's
looking at me and he's like
[Music]
and i'm like
and he's like yeah
and my family's like why do people order
it like this
[Laughter]
i was like i don't know but
this place
is awesome
i just i like crappy food too much i
love it
i love crabby i ate it of sonics today i
found the sonics
i thought it was a fictional restaurant
just in commercials
i need to venture to utah to find the
one sonic
that they advertise nationwide
come to the sonic off of the 15 in utah
new york city come on down
did it i found a sonic
got them tots got that shake baby
did it
love traveling this never fails every
time i go out of town i always just go
to a subway that's where i go i could go
anywhere when i go to the subway
i have one impression for you guys i
don't do a lot of impressions this is my
impression of somebody who works at
subway when you ask for a little
mayonnaise
someone works at somewhere when you're a
little
you're gonna get mayonnaise people
i figured out how to get a little
mayonnaise that stuff will you ask for
no mayonnaise you're still gonna get a
little squirt
like i don't want any mayonnaise manage
my sandwich please
we're still gonna try to squeak it in
there
[Laughter]
i swear i was on a subway a couple weeks
ago i ordered my sandwich i'm like look
buddy i don't want any mayonnaise i
don't like the mayonnaise it was a young
kid working the counter so he's like
[Laughter]
like no
no i reach on the sneeze no
and i swear to you he turned around to a
camera behind him
uh
[Laughter]
and i was mad
at first but then i looked at my
sandwich spelled in the mayonnaise and
said help me stuff that's going on
a couple summers back i was in high
school and i'm looking for just like a
crappy summer job you know something to
just hold me over
and you have like the jobs you want and
then you have like like the subway tier
i call it
it works on two levels because subways
are below the ground and because the
restaurant subway is not a place you
want to work
mine's called the subway tier anyway
did you guys see the subway they say
their chicken's only 50 50. you see that
only 50 chicken the other 50 percent
whatever you see that
i love subway i go to let me tell you
something i'm all about subway i love
subway but remember jared from subway he
lost 200 lbs on the subway diet he
dropped 200 pounds on the subway diet as
i emphasize it by hitting my leg
he lost how do you do that you can't do
that now that was back when subway was
just turkey on wheat but not anymore is
delicious you've been to subway lately
they got the philly cheese steak they
got the sweet onion chicken teriyaki oh
my gosh that is good on honey yolk you
think pound cake's ordering that your
dog on right that's what the pound cakes
order in
the sweet onion chicken teriyaki they
take that they put the salt they put the
sauce on there it's amazing but here's
my problem with going to subway come on
man hook me up i feel like i'm begging
you still have to go through that line
to get what you want on your sandwich i
was at subway earlier today uh would you
what would you like on your sandwich i
said i want some lettuce please
hmm
i feel like i'm having the best can i
get a little more
it's like what you bring the head of
lettuce from your house what are you
doing
is this your personal stash of lettuce
give me a glob of lettuce hook me up
ask for the sweet onion teriyaki sauce
drizzle drizzle
you think i won't look at me do i want a
drizzle of sweet onion chicken teriyaki
sauce hit me hard
when you go for the lettuce you're doing
i feel like i'm playing blackjack and
you're like hit me
hit me
i'm going to split these and double down
will you do that for me please
and here's the other situation if you
work at subway you're not an artist but
i'll call you one if that's what you
want to be
i'm you're an artist but do me a favor
won't you make my sandwich to make you
the way you make your personal employee
sandwich because i know what's happening
back there i know when you make your
employee sandwich you're doing it up
right when you see this dude in there
using his points card you got a problem
with that you're getting all skimpy on
that and you know you've got all
employees sitting back there double
hitting the bacon extra mayonnaise hey
fatty won't you make your sandwich the
way you went by man
i got a lot of attitude about subway i
don't know what happened
i apologize guys but sometimes it just
comes from the heart i'm on my legs i'm
doing elvis
my wife's family is rich they're loaded
my wife has an aunt
that she's a multi-millionaire she
bought a mansion in san diego that she's
not even gonna live in for five to ten
years she just bought this mansion for
later
for another time
not now
that's hard to relate to okay i can kind
of relate to it a little bit because
sometimes i go to subway
and i get a foot long sandwich
and i eat half right just half and i
save the other half for later
for another time
not now
that is a for later sandwich
you guys are fun i have tried a lot of
foods i did i tried to eat at subway
nine days in a row you ever do that
don't do that i had i had a moment of
clarity with subway i after nine days i
figured out that all the meats the same
they just have a guy that spray paints
in different colors in the back
story
one economy 40 kinds of bread though
which that can't be true right i think
there's two kinds of bread i think
there's white and wheat everything else
is something they made up that day they
get all excited try our new bread of the
week bedazzled pumpernickel
why is it sparkling
or it's a green you want nine grain 20
grain you want 40 grain bread
pretty soon it's just gonna be wood
right
yeah can i get a six inch turkey on is
that cedar
foot long roast beef on bamboo
yeah i wanna toast it and varnish give
it a good shellackin
all right you know what let's do a
little crowd work right that's an
important skill for comedian to have so
why don't i flex my crowd work muscle
real quick here uh you would what do you
do for a living
online fitness guy i don't have anything
for that okay
all right what about you buddy where do
you work
electrical engineering now
no
what
okay now i don't have any attorney stuff
does nobody work at subway
seriously nobody works at subway all
right you know what forget it
we're gonna edit this out no one worked
at subway you guys ruined it that's fine
we're gonna move on we'll move on what
else what else oh i was at subway the
other day
not a fan of subway let me tell you what
happened i went in there ordered my
sandwich ordered an m m cookie
it's a good cookie uh the guy gave me my
cookie it had
one m m in it
that is that is literally the least
amount of m ms that you can put in a
cookie and still legally call it
an eminem cookie
and at first i thought maybe it's a
mistake then i realized there's not a
mistake at all they know exactly what
they're doing because i replayed the
conversation in my head i said can i get
an m m cookie
and the guy goes one eminem cooking
not cool not cool
no i'm married i want to stay married i
had my anniversary last october i took
my bride out to one of those restaurants
where they make the food there right in
front of you
subway
it was hard man i used to work at
mcdonald's it's a terrible job but
people used to complain all the time at
mcdonald's can we agree as a room any
complaint that you have at mcdonald's
can be answered with it's mcdonald's
right
you know what you signed up for right
diarrhea why are we
why are you writing letters what's going
on
people get upset at me they're really
upset they're like uh sir excuse me i'm
like you don't have to call me sir okay
i'm a child
like sir excuse me but somebody's taking
a shower in the urinal
okay i just thought you should know that
i'm like yeah
it's mcdonald's
this ain't chick-fil-a right
yeah it's not my pleasure to be here i'm
a hostage okay
i should i feel like that should be
their slogan right
this thing chick-fil-a
you want ice cream psych our machine is
broken by the papa
i took this young lady out to go get
something to eat uh she really wasn't
that cute i'm gonna be honest so we
we end up at mcdonald's
[Music]
don't don't judge me sir you didn't see
her okay
you don't know you don't know what i had
to go through all right
uh
at the time my car
my car didn't exist i was broke i didn't
have one i didn't know it didn't uh she
was driving uh
we
we pull up to the drive-thru it's a very
romantic drive-through it's very well
lit and everything
we can see each other perfectly uh she
orders her food but dude couldn't hear
her
he said excuse me ma'am can you speak up
that's all he said to her she went
completely nuts
for no reason started yelling
immediately how did you get a job i know
your mama don't love you i said pickles
nerd
she went nuts
after she just finished cussing out the
mcdonald's drive-through dude
she gonna turn to me talking about so
mike what you want to get
uh wendy's now i'm not
i'm not ordering from this dude
why would you yell at him like that
i seen this movie it don't work out for
us in there
yeah drop me off guys i'm not
don't drop me off i'm not going away
with you drop me home
food is getting crazy out of control
like this happened a couple weeks ago i
went to a mcdonald's that salt shakers
on the tables at mcdonald's
who's eating mcdonald's going
you know what this needs
[Music]
it's a little bit more salt yeah
barely taste it on me
i think the hardest part traveling and
being a comic and it is it's more about
what you eat it's eating healthy and the
fast food industry is it's cheap it's
right there on the highway so it's hard
to resist it's the only industry in the
world by the way that can treat you like
garbage repeatedly and you still go back
[Music]
bad experience at a car dealership
insurance company you don't go back
there but everyone in here has a fast
food horror story even back to that same
location pretty happy about it
[Music]
i got a big mac at the drive-thru right
not a hard order not complicated there's
a couple layers
maybe an assembly line process
before i get back on the highway i reach
over it's really thin from my big mac
experience
i pick it up uh no meat
yeah that's a big part of the mac
the meat
so do i have this dilemma do i go back
inside and argue for my grade f beef
it actually made the sandwich healthier
i have a thousand island lettuce
sandwich
[Laughter]
the answer is yes you go back inside
you talk to the manager ted
ted this is embarrassing for both of us
i got no meat in my sandwich
the response i got from ted the manager
with a stray face was
are you sure
[Laughter]
no ted this is the big scam i got
running right now
i'm stealing patties from fast food
places
if you could pick it up i got 60 in the
car i got a wendy's to knock off two
exits down
i am the hamburglar
[Applause]
i think it's good to get fat shamed like
that though sometimes like i think
that's how he could help with childhood
obesity here's my idea i think
mcdonald's should make the play place
into a giant model of the human heart
that way when the fat kid gets stuck in
the aorta slide
he'll know what he has to look forward
to later in life
it'll be good for him
he'll have an epiphany in there be like
yeah i gotta change some things
cancel those nuggets mom
i'm all stuck up in here
my oldest child when he was five years
old uh man
we had a fun time we went to mcdonald's
and
the the manager was just having a bad
day right you could tell that it's like
this you know kind of take your order
just like just mad and it doesn't take
me any time at all to process oh i'm
gonna mess with this person
so there i am my five-year-old kid we're
trying to get something to eat at
mcdonald's
and this guy's all mad and ragey
and i said yeah i'll take you know the
big and tasty whatever meal i was
getting that day let me ask my son what
he
and that's gibberish just so you know i
have no idea
as a small child when we left
iran
and i never coached him into this i just
thought it'd be funny if i did that and
he looked at me
because he wanted
finally stopped
he wants a cheeseburger happy we'll
catch up on
for real
hey guys it's a hard language
my dad doesn't even email me at all
because you know he can't find the key
with the thank you
did you guys see this mcdonald's
announced they will no longer be using
styrofoam they'll be using cardboard i'm
thinking sooner or later they're gonna
have to use me
wow apparently mcdonald's fans in here
i'm sorry
like i like going to mcdonald's that's a
tough thing fast food man that is tough
sometimes i go to mcdonald's i don't
even buy anything it's the dopest way to
go by the way on a full stomach
i walk into mcdonald's and sometimes i
just look at the menu i watch it flip
over from breakfast to lunch
a tear comes to my eyes do you need
anything sir no just y'all back brought
back to mcrib i didn't know y'all gonna
do that i follow y'all on twitter y'all
didn't send that one out just kind of
caught me off guard
uh
the sandwich has no bones there's ribs
with no bones it's made by jesus that's
what that stands for
um
it's incredible
so now they put the calorie count in the
mcdonald's meal supposed to make you
feel bad about eating mcdonald's
i can't believe i've been eating all
these calories oh
personally i like to put the calorie
count in the mcdonald's menu because now
i know when i'm getting bang for my buck
you know what i mean
i order whatever has the most calories
in it that's the way i work the menu
i was like oh i only got two dollars oh
no let me get the two double
cheeseburgers yeah it's got the most
cows there yeah yeah it's a trick i
learned in jail watch your boy
um
look at the two double cheeseburgers do
you want a fish sandwich i don't want to
get that fish sarah shot it who's
ordering seafood at mcdonald's
it's not even real fish
it's a fish substance patty that they
make with tools and paper mache
that
fish sandwich out here
ordering seafood at mcdonald's who goes
to mcdonald's for seafood come on
you ever been sitting at home so i could
go some fish ooh mcdonald's got fish
sandwich on the dollar menu so there's a
fish
no
it's not even real fish
you ever look behind the mcdonald's
counter you ever see iron chefs back
there filleting fish
scaling fish where's the fish coming
from huh glitter tools paper mache tell
me
mcdonald's doesn't hire fisherman
i've never seen that sign in the window
want it now inquired in looking for a
cashier and a fly fisherman holding
tryouts on monday bring your own pole no
they don't need fishermen because they
make the fish in japan in between
sweatshop ships at the nike factory and
they email the fish here you enjoy the
fish
just don't die because if you die
they'll blame it on the fish
how do you die oh he don't eat the heap
of fillet o fish man
should have got it at the farmer's
market like me man he's just still here
but you know
gluten took him out
[Laughter]
what it is
stand like this mcdonald's in l.a not
too long ago the kid working behind the
counter had his pants pulled down a
little bit he had this uh bandana
hanging out of his pocket his mcdonald's
work hat tipped around the side
i said who are you with man the mccrips
but i had a little bit of that food i'm
content though because i i stopped and
had the best meal in my life i stopped
and had some mcdonald's
that's so so i don't think any adult
eats mcdonald's nowadays and when
they're done eating it they're like that
was delicious
i think even when kids eat mcdonald's
they're like my stomach hurts
[Music]
but i want to go back tomorrow right
what is in it
mcdonald's is the only food you eat and
you know you messed up when it's in your
throat it doesn't even have to get to
your stomach
you're like i gotta start making
mistakes what is this
[Music]
i don't care what fast food i eat if i
order french fries i have to eat every
fry
like i get depressed if the fries start
running out like i reach in the bag i'm
like i know there was more fries in this
bag
where's the rest of those fries then i
move the napkin out the way and i find
that one little burnt piece of crunchy
fry
i'm like that's what i'm talking about
baby right there
[Music]
my meal is complete right
before today i haven't been to
mcdonald's in like six or seven months
and i was cleaning out my car and i
found some french fries in between the
seats
yes and the fries look better than they
did the day that i bought them
i was like how is there no bacteria on
these fries
you know how bad of a food you have to
be for mold to be like i don't eat that
[Music]
that's a horrible food
someone was like did you eat the fries i
did lick one of them it was still salty
i didn't eat it though
i was like this is super salt how is it
still there
i was telling one of my friends about
that on the way here i was like yo i
found french fries in between my seats
she was like you found french fries she
was like i found a burger in between my
seats it was like a burger
i was like what like a wrapped up burger
she was like no just a patty i said who
loses a burger patty
in between their seats how dirty is your
car that you can lose a patty
i've never once went to mcdonald's who
was eating a cheeseburger and the meat
fell from between the bun
and i just kept eating it like oh i
guess this is just a ketchup onion
cheese mustard pickle sandwich
how did you lose the patty
uh i went to mcdonald's up the street
and i went to the drive-thru and i got
like a number two and i got up to the
window and this rather large lady leaned
out she goes 5.85 i was like at least
or whatever
i always do stuff like that i'll never
be able to lose the weight that i want
to lose as long as mcdonald's keep
randomly coming out with the mcgrib
i can't turn that down and i'm ashamed
of it
i've never loved a more indescribable
piece of meat before in my life
you ever see a migrant it's a creepy
sandwich buy one buy one take the bun
off of it see if he can get creeped out
comes out random times every six years
the mcrib is back
i'm pretty sure there's someone in the
back mcdonald's warehouse like man we
just found eight more boxes mcribs
where's the expiration date uh 1984 get
it out
it's still good
people try to defend it it's boneless
but the maiden look lock has got bones
it's creepy
the mcgreen was a human being to be a
pedophile that's how creepy there's just
hopping out of bushes badass
[Laughter]
oh and i have a lot of fat jokes i don't
have a problem with fat people i have a
problem with people who make excuses
right there's nothing i could have done
differently to be not a freak of nature
right
you know oh i'm i'm not fat i'm big
boned i'm big boned okay let's they're
gonna find my skeleton and think it was
a t-rex
i know i have a glandular problem i have
a glandular problem the mcdonald's is
not a gland
[Music]
mom
and i know she's going to watch this
special and just be like
i could go for a mcgland right now
dip that little barbecue little mcgland
uh like i said we went to went to italy
first time in europe first time in
europe it was uh
it was fun there's a lot of things that
people don't really know about at least
i didn't for one almost everybody in
europe smokes all the time it was
raining this was a very common
occurrence we had uh people would be
riding a bike while holding an umbrella
and a cigarette in the other hand
and we're just looking out of the
mcdonald's window like that's so
unhealthy
and i know a lot of people who have been
to italy get really angry when i tell
them that we went to mcdonald's
but just i just i had to have it i had
to have some that's the american embassy
right there mcdonald's
all that great food choices i'm like no
i'm gonna go with i'm gonna go with
mickey d's okay
and uh we're just you know i actually we
almost missed our train to venice
because of how badly i wanted to try
italian mcdonald's
it was an honest mixtape
here's a problem like i said i can't i
have a hard time talking to people like
just in general right i have like though
you ever have like the word word mumbles
you know i'm talking about like i think
i'm gonna say something but by the time
it's in my mouth it's all scrambled up
and weird right like i said i i didn't
want to go up to girl and hit on her and
be like hey girl
[Music]
um did you get that face at mcdonald's
because i'm loving it
[Music]
right
that's how it happens what happens is i
walk with the lady i'm like hey your
face looks like a chicken mcnugget
i got honey mustard in the truck you
want to take a dip
i just felt happy around her like i fell
around her how i do around cake that's
all
which that's the benefit of food over
people because you can tell food how you
feel
never gonna block you on instagram ever
never gonna do that
right you'll never see a mcdonald's
commercial where the guy's like i'm
loving it and all of a sudden ronald
mcdonald busted from the back
oh no oh love love okay well
we have other customers
i had a gig the other night i call it up
i'm like hey i'm almost home i'm
starving i'm going to stop and get a
mcdonald's mcdonald's i can't believe
you're still going there the fat
content's so high we don't know where
they get their beef get me a sundae
i did get stuck in line i don't know if
this is normal for around here there was
an older lady she was complaining about
everything that's happened over the last
six weeks
yeah she's probably still there right
now just going off on the cashier
like everything the weather the line the
prices there was no topic off bound
and then she said she said to the
cashier she goes last week i ate two big
macs and i wanted to kill myself
that's what she said
i whispered the guy in front of me i was
like i haven't eaten any big macs and i
want to kill her
come on sweep the leg get her out of the
way let's go
and then he whispered back that's my mom
he's like i want to kill her too
remember the good old days if you didn't
like to go to a restaurant you just
didn't go there again right if you
didn't like something you go you know
what i won't go back to wherever that is
again i won't go back to sizzler because
i didn't they didn't whatever but no we
got to get on our devices and we got to
chime in and we got to make sure that
everyone hears and they need to know
what i think and i'm going to give them
one star it's like we're trying to get
somebody fired relax get over yourself
give it a couple of months they'll get
their stuff together and then they'll
make a nice steak for you but in the
meantime don't be a whole nation of
whiner reviewers it is amazing to me
how
wow
and i would give that five stars what i
just said
but
no but everyone here's the deal you get
on yelp why are you trying to get
somebody fired from their gig my french
fries at mcdonald's were cold you know
what that's what you're gonna get
they're paying these guys 10 bucks an
hour what are you expecting you're
expecting ruth chris steakhouse it ain't
happening baby you know why you went to
mcdonald's because you're cheap that's
why
no but places you know like to try to
help are putting the calorie count on
menus you know so you go to fast food
restaurants like food item price calorie
count you know you guys have seen it
it's supposed to help you make a better
decision
let's just say it's never changed the
way i order
it's just changed the scenario
so now
when i'm at mcdonald's by myself
on a tuesday
at midnight
alone
[Music]
by myself
in my stretchies
it's like
hey mcdonald's employee
let's take this already low point in
both of our lives
and add about 1700 calories to it
and you better turn on that ice cream
machine sean you better turn it on
i think sometimes we give god credit for
stuff he doesn't want credit for
like uh recently had a friend pass away
suddenly and my other friends were like
why did god have to take jerry so soon i
guess you just need another angel in
heaven
i was like yeah yeah yeah maybe um
also jerry ate mcdonald's three meals a
day uh
[Music]
jerry did not take care of himself and
i think we got to meet him halfway uh
[Music]
i'm just saying if jerry is an angel in
heaven he's not one of the ones that fly
uh
that's all i'm saying
[Music]
maybe he does the books uh
it's gonna be different jobs right
i travel a lot and i i can't always eat
great you know because i'm like a like
i'm like a trucker hauling jokes and i
hit a lot of fast food and i hate fast
food i just i
hate the service i really hate how hard
is it to put a couple daggon napkins in
a bag
hey just for kicks tomorrow morning go
through the drive through at mcdonald's
and go
yeah i was here last night and uh
i think i left my kids in the playland
y'all see a couple kids running around
this morning y'all come in
why they look like sir like a mama
my wife a wife can't stand the service
you get to drive through she loves it
her idea her idea came home one day
she's like you still got that starting
pistol used back in high school when you
ran track oh yeah i was out in the
garage get it we're going mcdonald's
welcome mcdonald's gonna take your order
please
give me a two cheeseburgers two large
fries two large cokes i don't like
cheese it's fattening well shut the heck
up
everything okay after sir
i don't i'm sorry two cheeseburgers two
large fries two large cloves i want the
head coat look i don't need this the
first day i get out of jail i will use
his gun
you don't have the guts so i get the
starting pistol out
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah
make that one cheeseburger
[Applause]
can i get a couple extra napkins i don't
think the wrapper from the straw is
gonna cut it
try to eat all right better i mean but
it's all it's hard on the road some you
know they eat the fast food mcdonald's
burger king these places you know
sometimes you go to mcdonald's or burger
king sometimes if people work there
they're sharp you know they're sharp and
they're on the ball you know sometimes
sometimes other times you gotta wonder
you gotta wonder what that hiring
interview was like you know
please come in sit down
can you mumble
can you mumble can you mumble without
making eye contact
would you be willing to goof around with
your co-workers while the customer grows
impatient
great i think it'd be good candidate for
our management training program
we're going to have you watch an
eight-minute training video then we'll
put you on the front counter the
training video it'll show you how to jam
so many napkins into a dispenser
that people wouldn't be able to get one
out of the stick of dynamite
people get their own drinks now people
get their own drinks just gotta hand
them a cup and when you hand them a cup
when you hit them make sure your fingers
are sticking down inside the cup
that's our that's our policy
then you give them a bag of food and
you're all done there's no need to say
thank you because you wrote that on the
trash box
yeah it's we carved it into the trash
box they'll see that when they clean up
after themselves
i said i was trying earlier i think i
can be honest with you we both know i'm
not trying
like at all
that's how you look like this by not
trying every day
[Music]
today i went to mcdonald's
twice
first time was on purpose
i think the second was just a
combination of road hypnosis and muscle
memory
it's twice in the same day that's
nothing try going twice in the same
shift
that's a that's an experience right
there
you pull up to the menu order your food
they say pull around and you do because
you're hungry and obedient
and you get to the window and you see
that same person
recognize you from earlier
and just start questioning everything
you're like am i stuck in a time loop
or is this just the saddest man on the
planet
not being the regular at a diner or a
cafe that's cool you stroll in they
treat you like part of the family being
the regular at an arby's
is way less glamorous
you walk in there i got him again
better fire up the second fryer
i'm gonna get more curly fries out of
the freezer stop
i am from the south too i love being
southern i love the food i love the
people i love the hospitality my only
issue with the south everybody in the
south has an accent
a thick thick accent i was at a fast
food restaurant in south carolina i
decided to order in my best redneck
southern accent
when it came time i spoke into the
machine i was like hey
this is day y'all
will give me a dang ol number three make
it my way lettuce pickles tomatoes
cheese
top it off with a big old mountain dew
oh he's here awesome
i can't make this up person taking my
order comes that way
10-4 now this is cooter we read you loud
and clear brother
now now hey we gotta make it you're dang
all white cause you're the king here at
burger king
brother i'm gonna need you to pull
around the window number three cause man
we go
[Music]
guys when i pulled my car around the
person taking my order was chinese
that's a heck of an accent right there
taco bell recently announced i guess it
turns out it's the most healthy fast
food restaurant in america
that's a real sentence i just said
that blew my mind
honestly you guys because i know not one
person in the history of the world that
has walked into a taco bell and thought
i'm here to make good decisions
no
i've never seen a wine at the drive-thru
at taco bell in the daytime because
we're all waiting for the sun to go down
cause we're ashamed
cause taco bell tastes better between
the hours of two and three in the
morning when we're incapable of making
good decisions
no hate to taco bell totally love it if
they ever want to sponsor me i'm totally
down
i had a taco bell for lunch
which hey look i like it i like taco
bell i think
i think it's fine i think it's good
i just don't tell people i like it
because they always say the same thing
to me like you know it's not real
mexican food
like yeah there's a taco made out of a
dorito i got it
news flash folks nobody thinks taco bell
is real mexican food when you go into el
pollo loco nobody's like hey you know
those chickens aren't actually crazy
taco bell they they crack me up right
because
they know if you're gonna eat there
you're gonna eat there right nobody's on
the fence about taco bell nobody's like
well let's just wait and see what the
next commercial looks like you know
if you're gonna go back or not
and taco bell knows that that's why they
can put out a product that has the exact
same ingredients as three other products
on their current menu
they just change the name and or shape
of it
and we'll make you feel dumb for asking
about it
they're like what we have for the spring
this is seasoned steak lettuce cheese
tomato and sour cream encased in a flour
tortilla anybody have any questions
um yeah that sounds like a steak burrito
well it's not
okay the steak burrito is rolled up okay
with this we fold the sides in we press
it with a t-shirt iron i don't know
what's so hard to understand about the
technology we've invested in the
crunchwrap so what are we calling it to
crunchwrap
they're desserts they don't even try
with their desserts
they just take some other dessert you're
kind of familiar with and change it a
little bit you know
we have cinnabon bites
isn't that just a cut up cinnabon
i mean yeah but we cut it up for you
okay
you could say gracias
we took the time to put it into this
drink cup that was already sitting right
here
how much of the lifting do we have to do
[Music]
i remember a couple years ago
the hostess company went bankrupt and
then like a month later some mysterious
entity
saved them from bankruptcy i thought for
sure it was taco bell i was waiting for
that commercial
for years i was waiting for that
commercial right just
it's a twinkie burrito we have
stuffed a twinkie full of taco meat deep
fried it
sir would you like twinkie cream or sour
cream i don't care if it's coffee cream
i would like my twinkie burrito
some fire sauce
two ho ho loopers
and a mountain dew the blue mountain dew
too i want the baja
is that taco bell i'm not bragging i'm
just telling you where it was
behind the counter that a charity event
you can give a dollar on top of your
order and you know feel better about
yourself for 48
seconds but i don't want the attitude
when i don't want to give i place my
order she goes you want to give a dollar
to this charity you know it goes on top
of your order i'm like no i give him my
own way she goes she goes
i was like i'm sorry she goes you don't
care about people's health
i was like man i am eating a taco bell i
don't care about my own health
a lot of traveling with this job too man
um
gosh and just when you travel it's just
easy to eat fast food but i would eat
fast food if i wasn't traveling
because fast food's the best food um
taco bell is the best thing ever where's
my taco bell yes
[Applause]
love it
thank you like i love it i just don't
know what to do with it when people try
to ruin it for you like the healthy
people like when you eat it in front of
them
they're always like that's gross man
don't you know how they make that
and i'm like no
but i wish i would love to make this at
home like
save more money
i've got these friends they know i like
they make their own food they're weird
man um
they know i love the quesadilla at taco
bell and they're always like lee we can
make you a quesadilla that's better than
taco bell
i'm like yeah but
can i come to your house at 2 am and get
it
is that what you want me to drive to
your house to your window yell for food
at 1am
i'll do it
and
they try to groce you out with the
nutrition facts like we care
like but the meat they use it's a great
c meat it's grade c and i'm like you
know what i was a c student too
that is a passing grade we're doing just
fine
and
we get by on seas we're good
i was into one taco bell once before i
could order the guy at the counter he
stopped me he's like dude i just gotta
let you know something um the meat pump
is broken
the meat pump is that what you call your
toilet like
oh no we're at taco bell that makes
sense like
and that's the other stereotype i don't
care for that they always give on taco
bell oh taco bell makes a poop makes you
go to the bathroom i'm like what food
doesn't make you go to the bathroom
[Music]
when's there ever anything to brag about
like yeah i went to a vegan place last
month still hadn't pooped
let's see for the longest time i thought
ariana grande was a meal at taco bell
he's like it's not
[Music]
i thought that was the number six
mountain dew light ice let's go
what's happening today i love fast food
i went to taco bell for dinner tonight i
did that
oh you guys like it or um
[Laughter]
use my credit card to pay for it uh
because my career is on fire right now
how sad your life has become when you
have to finance a chalupa you know
you're like all right
zip it through see what happens
[Laughter]
i had this awkward moment with the lady
behind the counter because she asked if
she could see id with the credit card
just to make sure that the credit card
wasn't stolen
is that a thing in america now stealing
credit cards the first place you take it
is taco bell for real that's for you
we're gonna max this baby out
dollar 89 at a time
forget the plasma screen tv you morons
i'm going to make it rain chalupa
getting this party started
this is pretty awkward this has never
happened to me before i went through the
drive-through window today right got my
fast food bag
put it on the passenger car seat and the
passenger car seat belt light came on
it's like how much food did i order
if the car thinks there's another human
being in the car
still ate it it's fantastic
so good
i have been working in public education
for eight years
and i do not have a teaching license
[Laughter]
i'm not qualified for my job but i'm the
best one at it you can see the confusion
[Laughter]
like
imagine like as an adult i applied for a
taco bell
i did not get hired at the taco bell
which meant that i was not capable of
reheating bean pouches of diarrhea
but somehow i'm capable of teaching
walking bean pouches of diarrhea it's
crazy crazy
it's cool when i was in high school i i
was a big fan of spanish
and so when i was in high school i had
the opportunity to like go to mexico to
study abroad you know which was super
cool for like a spanish class which was
crazy
my parents say anything was a good idea
to send me anything it was safe so i
just did the next best thing
um i got a job in a taco bell
[Laughter]
so i'm gonna be fluent in like three
weeks you know what i'm saying
i'm kidding that's stupid that's stupid
that's a lot you guys know mexicans
don't work at taco bell you know that's
all black people all black people
and then white people working like
chick-fil-a or starbucks you know what
i'm saying
i think you're choosing chick-fil-a my
name's stacy how can i
help you today
it's crazy and i know black people work
at taco bell too because they're stingy
with their meat you know what i'm saying
you know what i'm talking about like
have you tried like doritos locos tacos
or whatever they give you like a little
bit of meat then throw a salad on top of
your taco i'm like devonta you better
take this bag
[Music]
devonte is a black person's name
that's why that's funny
here's a thing that happened recently i
laughed at my mom so hard in public that
she started yelling at me you know
here's the backstory have you ever by
the way laughing so hard like falling
down in the aisle at the grocery store
and i laughed here's what happened she
told me her dog had diabetes okay and i
started laughing so hard no it's so fat
of course it does you know
it's so big and she was like it's not
funny how could i have known he has
diabetes and i'm like probably because
he looks like a propane tank with legs
that's how
you know
there were so many clues
he's huge
of course he's diabetic and then also
you feed him people food all the time i
caught her feeding him doritos locos
tacos from taco bell once
it's like why are you why are you
feeding him the more expensive tacos you
know
she is true she goes he prefers them
what
did he tell you that
what is happening here also he's a
chihuahua we get it you know it's
ridiculous i saw this on the sign
outside mcdonald's the big sign the
marquee or whatever it said now hiring
apply inside
yeah apply inside apparently they've
determined that there's a big problem
[Music]
they come with potential employees
just driving right by
you know it's just just potential yeah
i'd like to get a job at that mcdonald's
but where do you where do you go to
apply
i don't know i think i think you go
downtown to the sheriff's department
it's all political
it's who you know
sometimes sometimes they put sometimes
you put this now hiring inquire within
that's pretty fancy language for a taco
bell isn't it did you ever talk like
that it's like shakespeare at the damn
side
i just want to go in there is the
manager within
oh manager oh manager where file dial
manager
surely within the confines of these
walls
to make chalupas or not to make chalupas
i was here yesterday to no avail
inquire within inquire within i guess
when you're gonna go you're gonna quit
you've got to give them your fortnight
notice you know
i shan't be returning
to be back
they have no idea the electronic trail
they leave everywhere on the phone on
the computer all day they don't realize
there's little footprints everywhere
sometimes easy to follow
i go to bed the other night do the
things that dads do turn off all the
lights
put the thermostat back where it goes
close the cabinets
go to sleep at 11 30 wake up at seven in
the morning there's a taco bell bag on
my counter
my boy comes in cracking nude what's up
you go out last night no
taco bell bag i don't know nothing about
that
really
i went on your bank account saw a charge
for taco bell
somebody must have stolen my card
so somebody broke into my house last
night
found your wallet took your atm card
cracked your pin code
spent three dollars
broke back into the house
replaced the card undetected left trash
on the counter
what do you think of that crime
dude slipped up
my dad is uh i'm mixed race actually my
dad is white from michigan and my mom is
white from ohio so it's uh yeah it's a
nice mix nice border joke some of you
got that okay very good
um so yeah it's it's fun but i i've
never gotten past food i you know um
drugs and alcohol aren't really
necessary you know when there's taco
bell
like i'm sorry it says
it's like now that heroin i'm gonna get
a mexican pizza you know this looks good
one of the ladies i work with she
challenged me she's like you know what
if you serious about getting in shape
you should try yoga
and i was like yoga
you can't challenge me to do something
and think i won't do it all right
so i did it i went to the yoga studio i
signed up problem was
i accidentally signed up for hot
power yoga
[Applause]
and if you don't know what hot power
yoga is let me tell you
they put you in there for 90 minutes
in a floor with just wood floor and
stuff like that and then they turn the
thermostat all the way up
you cannot challenge me to do anything
in this world without me preparing so on
my way to hot power yoga i stopped at
taco bell and got my usual
[Applause]
i love that guy back there
he's my new friend
so i'm in this class and we're about 45
minutes into it right and i'm in
downward dog at this point
and you think i'm sweating now
[Music]
lake havasu was forming underneath me
and the funny part about it there was a
really cute girl next to me and lake
havasu was getting closer
misty the instructor was like shaking
her head throughout the class
i was already mad because they don't
make yoga mats for fat people like me
okay
there was no cup holder for my diet
pepsi
about an hour into the class i hear this
misty focuses on me at this point in
time
they put me in the final position in the
final pose which is child's pose
huddled up in a little ball
you all know what a jake break sounds
like when it lets loose
it
misty's hair blew back like it was
hiroshima
people were running for the room
[Music]
point is i'm no longer welcome at hot
power yoga
[Music]
did something today i haven't done for a
long time went to a fast food restaurant
i haven't been to a fast food restaurant
in a million years because the last time
i went to a fast food restaurant i just
walked in asked the guy for a soda he
just handed me a cup
i just at they made me pour my own soda
just walked and asked him for a 7-up he
just
and i'm
this must be a diet seven
then he said did you want fries or that
and i said
i'm not if you're going to give me a
knife and a potato
i stood there being kind of stupid being
from out of town i'm always out of town
but and no
he just finally notes my convince sir
you pour it over there oh
oh i pour it
over there oh
thank you
thank you and next time i'm just gonna
bring a thermos i won't even have to
chat with you
i could have saved a buck in a quarter
and brought my own cup this time
what's next i'll be frying a burger at
home they're just gonna send me a bill
it's been a long day you're running
errands doing a bunch of stuff you get a
chance to get anything to eat on your
way home you decide let's stop at the
fast food place get some food and take
it back to the house and while ordering
your man turns to you and says would you
like some french fries
and you say no
that was your chance
there is no reason that once we pull to
the window they hand us the bag now we
can't drive with a bag so we hand you
the bag now it's a race to get home
because you're sitting there talking and
eating and talking and eating and those
are our fries
that is the sound of men who have lost
many a french fry
in the battlefield of life
i mean we love you to death ladies but
oh my goodness you getting there you
start eating and just talking
and in the middle you have this
realization you go you know what those
aren't even my fries you're right
they're not your fries
you had your chance
said this one night a woman looked me
dead in the face and said they taste
better when they're his
and every man's head in the room
exploded and every woman did exactly
what you did yeah that's right finally
someone put that into words that's
exactly right